Oranges and Sunshine is a drama, history film directed by Jim Loach.
The story of Margaret Humphreys, a social worker from Nottingham, who uncovers one of the most significant social scandals in
recent times – the forced migration of children from the United Kingdom to Australia and other Commonwealth countries.
Almost singlehandedly, Margaret reunited thousands of families, brought authorities to
account and worldwide attention to an extraordinary miscarriage of justice.
Margaret Humphreys, played by Emily Watson.
Susie, played by Aisling Loftus.
Jack, played by Hugo Weaving.
Nicky, played by Lorraine Ashbourne.
Len, played by David Wenham.
Pauline, played by Tara Morice.
Oranges and Sunshine is a 2010 biographical drama film directed by Jim Loach, in his directorial debut,
with a screenplay by Rona Munro, based on the 1994 book Empty Cradles by Margaret Humphreys.
The film stars Emily Watson, Hugo Weaving and David Wenham.
The tone is emotional.